<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EXT</title>
    <link>https://hobbysalike.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on EXT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hobbysalike.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Saints Row The Third - Nintendo Switch: A PC Gamer’s Perspective</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/saints-row-third-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/saints-row-third-switch/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Video is not uploaded/completed yet
A disclaimer for anyone that hasn’t played the storyline of this video game yet: I will not be going into too much detail of the story, characters or anything related besides my experience with the performance and visuals. There will be background video that may contain cutscenes or are from missions in the game, but should mostly be spoiler free.
Saints Row the Third, a game with a story everyone should play through at least once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you looking for a graphics card on a low budget?</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/blog/gpu-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/blog/gpu-test/</guid>
      <description>March 31st, 2022
Before even reading this, let me answer your question you may be asking. The graphics card you should purchase is the one you can afford. If you can&amp;rsquo;t afford the one you&amp;rsquo;re looking into and it&amp;rsquo;s a necessity to get a video card now, find one you can afford and settle with that for as long as possible. If it&amp;rsquo;s not neccesary to grab that one in specific and you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something more powerful, don&amp;rsquo;t get anything until you can afford it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Skip/Block Annoying Sponsors Inside YouTube Videos</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/youtube-adblock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/youtube-adblock/</guid>
      <description>Feb 14, 2022 Good morning. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to do this video, feeling it was very basic and little helpful for anyone else out there when it comes to the topic of ad blocks etc. But I decided hey, if it helps one other person, then my time wasn&amp;rsquo;t wasted.
Nobody likes ads, which is why most of us use an ad-blocker when we watch youtube and simply whitelist the channels we want to watch ads on to appreciate their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash;
crickets</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
