<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project EXT</title>
    <link>https://hobbysalike.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Project EXT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hobbysalike.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Saints Row The Third - Nintendo Switch: A PC Gamer’s Perspective</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/saints-row-third-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/saints-row-third-switch/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Video is not uploaded/completed yet
A disclaimer for anyone that hasn’t played the storyline of this video game yet: I will not be going into too much detail of the story, characters or anything related besides my experience with the performance and visuals. There will be background video that may contain cutscenes or are from missions in the game, but should mostly be spoiler free.
Saints Row the Third, a game with a story everyone should play through at least once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you looking for a graphics card on a low budget?</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/articles/gpu-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/articles/gpu-test/</guid>
      <description>Mar 31, 2022
Before even reading this, let me answer your question you may be asking. The graphics card you should purchase is the one you can afford. If you can&amp;rsquo;t afford the one you&amp;rsquo;re looking into and it&amp;rsquo;s a necessity to get a video card now, find one you can afford and settle with that for as long as possible. If it&amp;rsquo;s not neccesary to grab that one in specific and you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something more powerful, don&amp;rsquo;t get anything until you can afford it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it Worth Fixing an iPhone SE in 2022?</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/repair-iphone-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/repair-iphone-question/</guid>
      <description>Inititally written Feb 14, 2022, Uploaded Mar 6, 2022 Introduction Should you is a question too many people ask before even considering why they&amp;rsquo;re asking. But for some it feels impossible to get anywhere without asking, so I&amp;rsquo;m here today to hopefully answer your questions about whether its worth your time fixing older devices on your own, especially if you don&amp;rsquo;t plan to update them to the latest OS version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Skip/Block Annoying Sponsors Inside YouTube Videos</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/youtube-adblock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/youtube-adblock/</guid>
      <description>Feb 14, 2022 Good morning. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to do this video, feeling it was very basic and little helpful for anyone else out there when it comes to the topic of ad blocks etc. But I decided hey, if it helps one other person, then my time wasn&amp;rsquo;t wasted.
Nobody likes ads, which is why most of us use an ad-blocker when we watch youtube and simply whitelist the channels we want to watch ads on to appreciate their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple is Silently Killing Older iPhone Devices | iCloud Locked Until Update</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/apple-old-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/apple-old-ios/</guid>
      <description>Jan 26, 2022 Introduction Something useful to know before watching, Awhile back, Apple was reportedly slowing down older iPhone&amp;rsquo;s for reasons they claimed to save battery health &amp;amp; were eventually fined for doing this. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard anything about this, you should google up some articles about it before watching this video, because then whats coming up will make more sense.
IOS 15 &amp;amp; iCloud Apparently Apple no longer allows you to login to an iCloud account if your device is not on the latest IOS version (or at least IOS 15).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is It Worth Using the Oculus Quest 2 over AirLink?</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/articles/oculus-quest2-airlink/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/articles/oculus-quest2-airlink/</guid>
      <description>Jan 21, 2022
The other day, I was watching a Spawncast Live-stream late at night and one of the conversations were asking how the Oculus Quest 2 &amp;amp; PC would compare to the upcoming PSVR 2 and a PS5. The overall opinion was PSVR would be better because connecting to PC was either difficult or expensive, but that isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly true. For this video, I want to show you guys how to use an Oculus quest 2 wireless with Air Link and how it performs with games mentioned like Half Life: Alyx.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fastest BetterDiscord Setup Tutorial &amp; Best Plugins to Use</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/betterdiscord-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/betterdiscord-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Jan 12, 2022 I&amp;rsquo;ve been reluctant to make this video because I&amp;rsquo;m slower than your sex life on Tuesdays, but I had to reinstall Windows recently which also means I have to reinstall BetterDiscord. With that said, this video will show you the basics of how to install BetterDiscord &amp;amp; what plugins I recommend are basically a necessity.
Start by heading to BetterDiscord&amp;rsquo;s official website. All links will be in the video description as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Change Halo Infinite&#39;s Long Loading Screen</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/halo-intro-skip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/halo-intro-skip/</guid>
      <description>Jan 5, 2022 So awhile back, a couple months ago by the time I got around to writing this script, I posted a random video about Halo Infinite&amp;rsquo;s annoyingly long intro on my second channel. I didn&amp;rsquo;t put lots of effort into the video, even though I knew it would be gain some traction because at the time I was pretty sick and couldn&amp;rsquo;t care. My only real regret is not putting it on the main channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buying an iPhone 5S in 2022: Is It Worth It?</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/iphone5s-2022-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/iphone5s-2022-review/</guid>
      <description>Jan 4, 2022 Introduction Another day, another iphone from eBay. This time though, this device was bought from a trusted buyer that I&amp;rsquo;ve good experience with in the past.
only costing me roughly $20 free shipping. If the item was considered to be in good condition, they&amp;rsquo;d normally sell for $60 (That&amp;rsquo;s a big price difference). This listing though, stated there were issues with the LCD (the screen). Looking at all of the photos, there aren&amp;rsquo;t any signs that I can see that would concern me about issues with the LCD screen &amp;amp; figured maybe they&amp;rsquo;re just being picky with their item conditions &amp;amp; wanting to be more safe than sorry when selling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unboxing a FAKE iPhone SE from eBay for $1</title>
      <link>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/fake-iphonese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hobbysalike.com/youtube-uploads/fake-iphonese/</guid>
      <description>Sept 27, 2021 I buy a lot of stuff on eBay, most of the time items I think I can flip &amp;amp; make some money, or simply just want to keep around or actually use. So when I saw this listing for an iPhone SE with little-to-no description on what specs are inside starting at $1, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist. (It did get up to $20 because some other dude tried outbidding me but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t letting that happen shh).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
